{
    "subject": "resource/Eyemart_Express",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Eyewear_Retail",
    "human_readable": "Eyemart Express is a type of Eyewear Retail.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9559798240661621,
            "question": "Is Eyemart Express a type of store?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957326769828796,
            "question": "Can you find eyeglasses at Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7521047592163086,
            "question": "What kind of business is Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6887192726135254,
            "question": "What kind of service does Eyemart Express provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6881355047225952,
            "question": "Is Eyewear Retail a category of stores?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6490394473075867,
            "question": "What industry is Eyemart Express part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378859639167786,
            "question": "What products does Eyemart Express sell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4924321472644806,
            "question": "Where would you go to buy glasses at Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25114601850509644,
            "question": "Give an example of a place you might buy eyewear."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24281048774719238,
            "question": "What is another term for an eyeglasses store?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eyemart Express is a type of Eyewear Retail.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1283_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a place you might buy eyewear.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1283_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go to buy glasses at Eyemart Express?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1283_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products does Eyemart Express sell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1283_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1283_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information clearly states that Eyemart Express is an \"eyewear retailer\", and provides various details about their business, such as their wide variety of frames, affordable prices, and commitment to customer satisfaction. This suggests that the triple statement is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Eyemart Express as an eyewear retailer, which supports the statement that Eyemart Express is a type of eyewear retail."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}